Vi har blivit väldigt vana med internet.
Vi delar ständigt med oss information om oss själva och våra privatliv.
Vilken mat vi äter, vilka vi träffar,
platser vi besöker och vad vi läser.
Låt mig förklara lite utförligare.
Just nu, om någon försöker kolla dig,
så kommer de hitta din identitet, din position, ditt operativsystem,
alla sajter du besökt, vilken webbläsare du använder,
och mycket mer information om dig och ditt liv
som du antagligen inte tänkte dela med främlingar,
som enkelt kan använda detta för att utnyttja dig.
Men inte om du använder Tor!
Tor Browser protects our privacy
and identity on the Internet.
Tor secures your connection
with three layers of encryption
and passes it through three voluntarily
operated servers around the world,
which enables us to communicate
anonymously over the Internet.
Tor also protects our data
against corporate or government targeted
and mass surveillance.
Perhaps you live in a repressive country
which tries to control and surveil the Internet.
Or perhaps you don't want big corporations
taking advantage of your personal information.
Tor makes all of its users
to look the same
which confuses the observer
and makes you anonymous.
So, the more people use the Tor network,
the stronger it gets
as it's easier to hide in a crowd
of people who look exactly the same.
You can bypass the censorship
without being worried about
the censor knowing what you do
on the Internet.
The ads won't follow you
everywhere for months,
starting when you first
clicked on a product.
By using Tor, the sites you visit
won't even know who you are,
from what part of the world
you're visiting them,
unless you login and tell them so.
By downloading and using Tor,
you can protect the people
who need anonymity,
like activists, journalists and bloggers.
Download and use Tor! Or run a relay!